So which other change can we implement? Let's have a look at our layout component, in the layout folder
Wic jak redni zmian moemy zaimplementowa? Przyjrzyjmy si naszemu komponentowi layoutu w folderze layoutu i
under components. If we have a look at it, it's clearly a class based component and it has a state, a state
komponentach, jeli przyjrzymy si temu, e jest to wyranie komponent oparty na klasach i ma
to handle their display of the sideDrawer.
stan, w ktrym mona obsuy wywietlanie elementu decydujcego.
Now I don't really consider it to be a container, though you could argue for it to be one because obviously
Teraz naprawd nie uwaam tego za pojemnik, chocia mona by twierdzi, e jest to pojemnik,
it contains some other components and it passes states down to them,
poniewa oczywicie zawiera on inne skadniki i przekazuje je pastwom.
so it wouldn't necessarily be wrong to place that layout component here in their containers folder
Tak wic niekoniecznie byoby niewaciwe umieszczanie tego komponentu tutaj w folderze z jego
like this
kontenerami.
so now I'll move it over there.
Teraz przenie to tam.
You could also argue for something different with the given folder structure which of course is only
Mona rwnie argumentowa za czym innym z podan struktur folderw, co oczywicie jest
just one possible way where I have this hoc folder for higher order components,
tylko jednym z moliwych sposobw, w ktrych mam ten staroytny folder dla komponentw wyszego rzdu.
you could kind of argue that a layout is really just a higher order component,
Mona twierdzi, e ukad jest tak naprawd tylko elementem wyszego rzdu.
because what you're doing with it is you're wrapping your other components with the layout.
Poniewa to, co robisz, to pakujesz swoje rednie komponenty w ukad.
So the burger builder component in our application but once we add routing, that of course are going to
Wic skadnik Burger Burger w naszej aplikacji, ale gdy dodamy routingu, e oczywicie
be more components.
bdzie wicej skadnikw.
And in the app.js folder, we're really just wrapping the burger builder with our layout component
I rzeczywicie jest peniejszy, tak naprawd po prostu owijamy budowniczego burgera naszym warstwowym komponentem.
and this essentially makes it a higher order component.
A to zasadniczo sprawia, e jest to komponent wyszego rzdu.
These are maybe just semantics,
To moe tylko semantyka.
it doesn't really change the way your application work, how you call your components.
To tak naprawd nie zmienia sposobu dziaania aplikacji w jaki sposb wywoujesz swoje komponenty.
Still you could move layout into containers or you could move it into hoc or maybe in your application,
Nadal mona przenie dozwolone do pojemnikw lub mona przenie go do H O C, a moe w aplikacji.
you don't really have a hoc folder,
Tak naprawd nie masz folderu HELOC.
maybe there, you just have containers and components.
Moe tam wanie masz pojemniki i komponenty.
There is more than one correct way,
Istnieje wicej ni jeden poprawny sposb.
now I like this set up though where layout is now in the hoc folder because I consider it a higher
Teraz podoba mi si ta konfiguracja, chocia ukad jest teraz w folderze H O C, poniewa uwaam go za
order component,
komponent wyszego rzdu.
it's only there to wrap other components and therefore here we're using it in app.js to wrap whichever
Jest tam tylko do zawijania komponentw Abra i dlatego uywamy go i aptest, aby zawrze dowoln
route we're rendering
tras, ktr renderujemy.
hence I move it into the hoc folder.
Dlatego przenosz go do folderu HLC.
Now I will also create a new subfolder in hoc
Teraz bd te uywa podfolderw w HUAC.
therefore, the aux folder and move my aux.js file in there.
W zwizku z tym folder ukw i przenie tam mj plik poszukiwa ukw.
Now this of course will lead to some errors because now we will have some import issues. In the layout
Teraz to oczywicie doprowadzi do pewnych bdw, poniewa teraz bdziemy mie pewne problemy z importowaniem w folderze
folder, we'll need to adjust our imports to still have correct paths to all the components we depend
ukadu, musimy dostosowa nasze importowanie, aby nadal mie poprawne pauzy do wszystkich skadnikw, od ktrych
on and we'll have to make sure that wherever we're importing aux, we also adjust the path.
jestemy zaleni, i bdziemy musieli upewni si, e wszdzie importujemy Oxxa, dostosowujemy take POF.
So let's quickly do that,
Zrbmy to szybko.
I'll start the layout component and I'll start with the aux import since layout is hoc and aux's,
Zaczn komponent ukadu i zaczn od importu od czasu Laodicea HAMC i oxes.
we only have to go up one level now to go into the hoc folder, so we can remove that part
Musimy przej tylko o jeden poziom wyej, aby przej do folderu AOC, abymy mogli usun t cz.
we already are in there and then move into the aux folder and then import the aux.js file,
Ju tam jestemy, a nastpnie przenosimy si do folderu alkw, a nastpnie importujemy spadki zawartoci ox.
so this is how we need to adjust this.
To wszystko, czego potrzebujemy, aby to zmieni.
The classes import doesn't change of course because there's css files in the same folder but the toolbar
Importowanie Klaas nie zmienia si oczywicie dlatego, e jest tak szybki jak w tym
import does change, there we need to go all the way up then into the components folder and then we
samym folderze, ale import paska narzdzi nie zmienia si tam musimy przej ca drog do folderu komponentw,
can go into the navigation folder and I can basically copy that part here prior to navigation from the
a nastpnie moemy przej do folderu nawigacji i Zasadniczo mog skopiowa t cz tutaj przed nawigacj z paska
toolbar import and also use it here for the sideDrawer.
narzdzi, a take uy jej tutaj w bocznej szufladzie.
So with that, the layout component is updated,
W zwizku z tym komponent ukadu jest aktualizowany.
Now what I also do is I need to restart and give a start because it seems to break on that aux file
Teraz to, co robi, to trzeba zrestartowa i ludzie zaczynaj, poniewa wydaje si, e ami to alki, na ktre
which it really shouldn't,
tak naprawd nie powinno.
but we'll probably also get some other errors here because we're importing aux
Ale prawdopodobnie dostaniemy tu rwnie inne strzaki, poniewa importujemy Oxx.
in other files. In the app.js file,
Arafat rzeczywicie tak jest.
we also need to adjust the import for the layout component
Wszyscy musimy dostosowa import do przodu komponentu ukadu.
it's of course now in the hoc folder,
To oczywicie teraz w folderze HAMC.
so that is something we should adjust.
Dlatego powinnimy to zmieni.
Then in the burger builder as you can see here in the error message, we got to an error because there
Nastpnie w Bergere Boulder, jak mona zobaczy tutaj w komunikacie aero, doszo do
in the burger builder we are of course using the aux component.
bdu, poniewa s one w Bergere Boulder, oczywicie uywamy skadnika ox.
So there we need to adjust the import because now it's essentially still in the hoc folder
Musimy wic dostosowa import, poniewa teraz jest on w dalszym cigu w folderze HLC.
but we created that aux subfolder which we need to adjust. In the sideDrawer component, there
Ale stworzylimy podfolder alks, ktry musimy dostosowa w bocznym losowaniu lub komponencie.
we also are using aux and there we also have to go to the aux folder and import the aux.js file from
Uywamy rwnie Oxx i tam musimy rwnie przej do folderu ox i zaimportowa do niego
there. In the modal component which is in the UI folder, there we also use aux
plik dostpowy w komponencie modalnym, ktry znajduje si w folderze UI tam uywamy rwnie alkw.
so we also need to add slash aux at the end here, and in the order summary, we face a similar issue,
Wic na kocu musimy rwnie doda slash aleks, a w podsumowaniu zamwienia napotykamy podobny problem.
there we also need to import the aux file from within the aux folder
Tam musimy rwnie zaimportowa spadek w z folderu skrzynki.
and with all these changes, now we should have a working application again.
I po tych wszystkich zmianach powinnimy znw mie dziaajc aplikacj.
Let's quickly check if it does work,
Sprawdmy szybko, czy to dziaa.
it's looking good.
Wyglda dobrze.
So now we got an application which works again without throwing any errors
Teraz mamy aplikacj, ktra dziaa ponownie, nie rzucajc adnych bdw.
but now with our new folder structure, which is optional but which makes more sense in my opinion since
Ale teraz z nasz now struktur folderw, ktra jest opcjonalna, ale ktra ma wicej sensu w mojej opinii, poniewa jeste
or due to the way our components do work. Now with that, we really have a great application,
zwizany ze sposobem, w jaki nasze komponenty dziaaj teraz z tym, e mamy naprawd wietn aplikacj.
let's now move on with this course.
Przejdmy teraz do tego kursu.